bollysite.com 2017-12-15

# Bollysite privacy policy

* * *

We respect your privacy and We am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site [www.bollysite.com](http://www.bollysite.com/). The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

## Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers, We use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

## E-mail Subscription

If a user wishes to subscribe to our posts via e-mail (powered by Feedburner), We ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. My site use cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, We have no access to or control over these cookies, once We have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section. Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

## Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that We am not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

## Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and We do not have access to these information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense and MKhoj. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. 

## Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact me by emailing at our-domain at gmail com. 

* * *
